(
"ai_sub_version": "2.6.1b1",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 2,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 14,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"web_search_tool": "duckduckgo",
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": "libx264"
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
くわ！ こゆりだよ！
Kowa! It's Koyuri!
せーの！
Ready, go!
こんこよべーすと！
Konkoyo Best!
はい！ ハッシュタグ
Yes! Hashtag
#こより実験中 リサーチしてね
#KoyoriExperimenting, please research!
OK!
こよは 助手くんの 助手ですが？
I'm your assistant's assistant?
はい やったー！
Yes, yay!
こよりスケッチ 照れちゃう
Koyori Sketch, I'm blushing
はい 萌え！ せーの！
Yes, moe! Ready, go!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
勉強中だし 全力投球
I'm studying and giving it my all
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
今日も こよりは 絶好調
Koyori is in top form today too
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
こよりの朝食は マヨネーズ
Koyori's breakfast is mayonnaise
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
こんこわ！ ヘルプ！
Konkowa! Help!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
わー！ どんこゆー
Whoa! Donkoyu-
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
助手くんなんだねー！ 見つけたー！
You're my assistant! Found you!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
可愛いでしょー！ えへへー！
I'm cute, right? Ehehe!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
OK! こんこよべーすと！
OK! Konkoyo Best!
わーー！
Waaaa!
やったー！ 間に合ったー！
Yay! I made it!
マヨネーズは 飲み物です
Mayonnaise is a drink
ちなみに 助手が 大好きです
By the way, I love my assistants
はい！ お肉！ 全開！
Yes! Meat! Full power!
冷凍うどんは 常備してます
I always have frozen udon stocked
どうですか？
How's that?
はい やったー！
Yes, yay!
証明完了 Q.E.D.
Proof complete, Q.E.D.
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
ココアだ！ こくこく
It's cocoa! Gulp, gulp
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
お昼寝は 午後のしるし
A nap is the sign of the afternoon
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
お肉食べる？ ういーういーういー！
Want to eat meat? Oui oui oui!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
あー！ いけませんねー！
Ah! That's not good!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
思い出しちゃうなー
I'm starting to remember
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
僕らのプログラムは 溶けていく
Our programs are melting away
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
あー！ こゆだよ！
Ah! It's Koyu!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
うーー！ っしゃー！
Uuu! Shaa!
はい！はい! はい！はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
やったー！ 間に合ったー！
Yay! I made it!
マヨネーズは 飲み物です
Mayonnaise is a drink
ちなみに 助手が 大好きです
By the way, I love my assistants
はい！ お肉！ 全開！
Yes! Meat! Full power!
冷凍うどんは 常備してます
I always have frozen udon stocked
どうですか？
How's that?
はい やったー！
Yes, yay!
私の戦闘力は 54万です
My power level is 540,000
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
あ、お掃除は 週一です
Ah, cleaning is once a week
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
雨降って 落ち着いちゃうんだよ
It's raining and I'm feeling calm
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
竹の子派です きのこ好き！
I'm on Team Takenoko! I like mushrooms!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
わー！ 150、50！
Whoa! 150, 50!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
シャンプーは 飲み物ではありません
Shampoo is not a drink
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
豚骨ラーメン 好きー！
I love tonkotsu ramen!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
しっぽも 振っちゃダメですよ
Don't wag your tail either
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
みんなの応援が 必要だよ！
I need everyone's support!
右手ーー！
Right hand!
やったー！ 間に合ったー！
Yay! I made it!
マヨネーズは 飲み物です
Mayonnaise is a drink
ちなみに 助手が 大好きです
By the way, I love my assistants
はい！ お肉！ 全開！
Yes! Meat! Full power!
冷凍うどんは 常備してます
I always have frozen udon stocked
どうですか？
How's that?
はい やったー！
Yes, yay!
せーの！ こんこよー！
Ready, go! Konkoyo-!
くわ！ こゆりだよ！
Kowa! It's Koyuri!
せーの！
Ready, go!
こんこよべーすと！
Konkoyo Best!
はい！ ハッシュタグ
Yes! Hashtag
#こより実験中 リサーチしてね
#KoyoriExperimenting, please research!
OK!
こよは 助手くんの 助手ですが？
I'm your assistant's assistant?
はい やったー！
Yes, yay!
こよりスケッチ 照れちゃう
Koyori Sketch, I'm blushing
はい 萌え！ せーの！
Yes, moe! Ready, go!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
勉強中だし 全力投球
I'm studying and giving it my all
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
今日も こよりは 絶好調
Koyori is in top form today too
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
こよりの朝食は マヨネーズ
Koyori's breakfast is mayonnaise
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
こんこわ！ ヘルプ！
Konkowa! Help!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
わー！ どんこゆー
Whoa! Donkoyu-
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
助手くんなんだねー！ 見つけたー！
You're my assistant! Found you!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
可愛いでしょー！ えへへー！
I'm cute, right? Ehehe!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
OK! こんこよべーすと！
OK! Konkoyo Best!
わーー！
Waaaa!
やったー！ 間に合ったー！
Yay! I made it!
マヨネーズは 飲み物です
Mayonnaise is a drink
ちなみに 助手が 大好きです
By the way, I love my assistants
はい！ お肉！ 全開！
Yes! Meat! Full power!
冷凍うどんは 常備してます
I always have frozen udon stocked
どうですか？
How's that?
はい やったー！
Yes, yay!
証明完了 Q.E.D.
Proof complete, Q.E.D.
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
ココアだ！ こくこく
It's cocoa! Gulp, gulp
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
お昼寝は 午後のしるし
A nap is the sign of the afternoon
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
お肉食べる？ ういーういーういー！
Want to eat meat? Oui oui oui!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
あー！ いけませんねー！
Ah! That's not good!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
思い出しちゃうなー
I'm starting to remember
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
僕らのプログラムは 溶けていく
Our programs are melting away
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
あー！ こゆだよ！
Ah! It's Koyu!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
うーー！ っしゃー！
Uuu! Shaa!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
やったー！ 間に合ったー！
Yay! I made it!
マヨネーズは 飲み物です
Mayonnaise is a drink
ちなみに 助手が 大好きです
By the way, I love my assistants
はい！ お肉！ 全開！
Yes! Meat! Full power!
せーの！ こんこよー！
Ready, go! Konkoyo-!
こよりは　マヨネーズ　で　回復　した
Koyori recovered with mayonnaise.
助手くんが仲間になった！
Joshu-kun became an ally!
AIこよりが仲間になった！
AI Koyori became an ally!
もふこよが仲間になった！
Mofukoyo became an ally!
ヘイ！
Hey!
カロスを照らすあの朝日のように
Like that morning sun shining on Kalos,
（ニトロチャージ、熱く行こうぜ）
(Nitro charge, let's go hot!)
さあ！進もうぜ、いつでも準備はOK
Come on! Let's move forward, we're always ready,
（型破り、変幻自在で）
(Unconventional, changing freely!)
重なり合う思いが、奇跡を呼び起こす
Our overlapping feelings will summon a miracle...
XY&Z！
XY&Z!
いくぜ！激しく燃えるバトル
Let's go! An intensely burning battle!
いくぜ！ピンチはチャンスだぜ
Let's go! A pinch is our chance!
いくぜ！起死回生
Let's go! A miraculous turnaround,
絶対に諦めない
I will never give up!
ヘイ！たとえどんな壁が道を塞いだって
Hey! No matter what walls block our path,
いつでもぶつかって砕けるだけで
We'll always just smash right through them.
さあ！この手で勝利の星を掴むんだ
Come on! I'll grab the star of victory with these hands,
折れない不屈の心で
With an unbreakable, indomitable heart.
博衣こより生誕ライブ2026、見に来てくれてありがとう！
Thank you for coming to Hakuikoyori Birthday Live 2026!
神ゲーたちの神ゲーソングをいっぱい詰め込んでるの。最後まで楽しんでいってね！
I've packed it with god-tier songs from god-tier games. Enjoy until the very end!
いくぜ！激しく燃えるバトル
Let's go! An intensely burning battle!
いくぜ！ピンチはチャンスだぜ
Let's go! A pinch is our chance!
いくぜ！起死回生
Let's go! A miraculous turnaround,
絶対に諦めない
I will never give up!
はーい！みんなこんこよー！
Hi! Hello everyone, Kon-koyo!
ホロライブ6期生、秘密結社HoloXの頭脳、博衣こよりだよ！
I'm the brain of Secret Society HoloX, Hololive's 6th Gen, Hakuikoyori!
改めて今日は博衣こより生誕ライブ2026にお越しいただきありがとうございます！
Once again, thank you for joining Hakuikoyori Birthday Live 2026 today!
コメントもいっぱいありがとう！イエーイ！こっ、こよ、見えてるよ、ありがとう！
Thanks for all the comments! Yay! I see you, Kok-koyo, thank you!
ということで、ライブの感想やスクショはハッシュタグ #博衣こよ生誕Live2026 をつけてたくさん...
So, please share your thoughts and screenshots with the hashtag #HakuikoyoriBirthdayLive2026!
ポストしてください！
Please post about it!
目指せトレンド1位、よろしくだああ！
Let's aim for trending #1! Here we go!
はい、ということで。ちょっと、息が整ってないですけど...
Alright! I'm a bit out of breath, but...
さて、今年の生誕ライブ、テーマは...
Well, the theme for this year's birthday live is...
「ゲームソングライブ」です！
"Game Song Live"!
これまでたくさんやってきた実況配信で、一緒に遊んできた思い出のゲームや...
From the many game streams we've done together, full of memories...
こよが大好きをゲーム関連の楽曲をたくさん詰め込みました。
...I've packed in lots of game-related songs that I love.
最後まで全力で楽しんでってね！
Enjoy it with all your might until the very end!
ということで、1曲目は大好きなポケモンの...
So, for the first song, I sang my favorite Pokemon's...
「XYZ」を歌わせていただきました！ねー！
"XYZ"! Right?!
助手くん、わー！
Joshu-kun, wah!
「俺はこいつと旅に出る」っていうことです。
It means "I'm going on a journey with this guy."
はい、Xでセトリ予想もね、みんなにたくさんしてもらってたんですけど...
I saw all your setlist predictions on X, but...
ポケモンの予想は結構多かったけど、XYZ当てられてる人は結構少なかったです。
There were many Pokemon guesses, but very few people got "XYZ" right.
当たった君、おめでとう！
To those who got it, congratulations!
まぁこの曲は、Z-Aが発表になったっていうのもあるんですけど...
Well, this song... partly because Pokemon Z-A was announced...
歌詞がめっちゃ良くて、実はこよりにもぴったりな曲なので選びました。
But the lyrics are so good, and it's actually perfect for Koyori, so I chose it.
さぁ、この後も、自分の予想が当たってるかなーって、ドキドキしながら楽しんでいってください。
Now, please keep enjoying and see if your predictions come true!
新3Dお披露目もあるからね！
There's also a new 3D reveal!
絶対に最後まで見てってね！
Make sure to watch until the very end!
それでは、そろそろ次の曲。
Now, time for the next song.
ゲームの世界へ、どうぞ！
Off to the game world we go!
エアーマンが倒せない
I Can't Defeat Airman
気がついたら　同じ面ばかりプレイ
Before I knew it, I was playing the same stage again and again
そしていつも　同じ場所で死ぬ
And I always die in the same spot
あきらめずに
Without giving up,
消える足場に挑戦するけど
I'll keep jumping on the vanishing platforms,
すぐに下に落ちるよ
But I immediately fall down
アイテム2号があれば 楽に 向こうの 岸まで 着くけれど
If only I had Item 2, I could easily reach the other side...
何回やっても 何回やっても
No matter how many times I try,
エアーマンが倒せないよ
I can't defeat Airman!
あの竜巻 何回やっても 避けれない
I can't dodge those tornadoes, no matter how many times I try
後ろに回って 打ち続けても
Even if I get behind him and keep firing,
いずれは風に飛ばされる
I'll eventually be blown away by the wind
タイム連打も 試してみたけど
I even tried rapid-pausing,
竜巻相手じゃ 意味がない
but it's useless against the tornado
だから次は絶対 勝つために
So, to ensure a win next time,
僕はE缶だけは 最後までとっておく
I'll save my E-Tanks until the very end!
気がついたら ライフも 少ししかない
Before I knew it, I had very little life left
そしていつも そこでE缶使う
And I always end up using an E-Tank there
あきらめずに エアーマンまで たどり着くけれど
I don't give up and manage to reach Airman...
すぐに 残機 なくなる
...but I immediately run out of lives
リーフシールドがあれば 楽に エアーマンを 倒せるけど
If only I had the Leaf Shield, I could easily defeat Airman, but...
何回やっても 何回やっても
No matter how many times I try,
ウッドマンが倒せないよ
I can't defeat Woodman!
落ちるこの葉 何回やっても 避けれない
I can't dodge those falling leaves, no matter how many times I try
後ろに下がって 距離をとっても
Even if I back away and keep my distance,
いずれは距離を詰められる
he eventually closes in
タイム連打も 試してみたけど
I even tried rapid-pausing,
あいつのジャンプは くぐれない
but I can't slide under his jumps
だから次は絶対 勝つために
So, to ensure a win next time,
僕はE缶だけは 最後までとっておく
I'll save my E-Tanks until the very end!
アイテム2号があれば 楽に 向こうの 岸まで 着くけれど
If only I had Item 2, I could easily reach the other side...
何回やっても 何回やっても
No matter how many times I try,
エアーマンが倒せないよ
I can't defeat Airman!
何回やっても 何回やっても
No matter how many times I try, no matter how many times I try,
エアーマンが倒せないよ
I can't defeat Airman!
後ろに回って打ち続けても
Even if I get behind him and keep shooting,
いずれは風に飛ばされる
I'll eventually be blown away by the wind.
タイム連打も試してみたけど
I even tried spamming the Time Stopper,
竜巻相手じゃ意味がない
but it's useless against the tornadoes.
だから次は絶対勝つために
So next time, to make sure I win,
僕はE缶だけは最後まで取っておく
I'll save my E-Tanks until the very end.
倒せないよー
I can't defeat him!
ロボのテーマ / 作曲：光田康典
Robo's Theme / Composition: Yasunori Mitsuda
R・O・B・O
R-O-B-O
ロボのテーマ
Robo's Theme
鋼の体 夢を乗せて
Steel body, carrying dreams,
未来を拓く 戦士なのさ
a warrior who opens the way to the future.
壊れた心 直してくれた
You repaired my broken heart,
優しい君の 笑顔守る
I'll protect your kind smile.
遥か時空を 越えてゆこう
Let's go beyond far-off space-time,
終わらない旅 続けよう
let's continue this never-ending journey.
奇跡の歌を 響かせて
Let the song of miracles resonate,
愛を届ける ロボのテーマ
delivering love, Robo's Theme.
R・O・B・O
R-O-B-O
ロボのテーマ
Robo's Theme
カエルのテーマ / 作曲：光田康典
Frog's Theme / Composition: Yasunori Mitsuda
勇気を胸に 剣を抜け
Draw your sword with courage in your heart,
呪われた身の 騎士ならば
if you are a knight in a cursed body.
誇り高き その魂
That high-proud soul,
悪を貫く 閃光となれ
become the flash that pierces evil.
カエル！
Frog!
正義のヒーロー
Hero of justice.
水面を跳ねて 闇を裂け
Leap across the water and tear through the darkness,
勝利の旗を 掲げよう
let's raise the flag of victory.
友との絆 忘れない
I won't forget the bond with my friend,
誓いのメダル 輝かせて
make the Medal of Vow shine.
時代の風を 追い越して
Overtake the winds of the era,
明日へ駆ける カエルのテーマ
running toward tomorrow, Frog's Theme.
カエル！
Frog!
カエルのテーマ
Frog's Theme
Melodies Of Life / 作詞：シオミ 作曲：植松伸夫
Melodies Of Life / Lyrics: Shiomi, Composition: Nobuo Uematsu
あてもなく彷徨っていた
Wandering aimlessly,
手がかりもなく探し続けた
searching without a clue.
あなたがくれた思い出を
The memories you gave me,
心を癒す歌にして
turning them into a song to heal my heart.
約束の場所へ
To the promised place...
いつか
someday.
歌にして
...into a song to heal the heart.
約束も無く 交わす言葉も
With no promise, and words we exchanged...
決めることさえせず 抱きしめ
...without even deciding, we held each other tight.
そして確かめた日々は
And the days we spent together...
二度とは帰らぬ
...will never return.
記憶の中の 手を振るあなたは
In my memories, you reaching out to me...
私の名を呼ぶことができ
...can you still...
きるの？
...call out my name?
溢れるその涙を
Those overflowing tears...
輝く夢に替えて
...change them into a shining dream.
命は続く
Life goes on,
夜を越え
crossing the night,
疑うことのない明日へと続く
to a tomorrow without doubt...
続く
...it continues.
飛ぶ鳥の向こうの空へ
To the sky beyond the flying birds,
幾つの記憶預けただろう
how many memories did I entrust?
はかない希望も夢も
Fleeting hopes and dreams,
届かぬ場所に忘れて
forgetting them in an unreachable place.
めぐりあうのは
Our meeting,
偶然と言えるの？
can we call it coincidence?
分かってる
I know.
時が必ずくれる
Time will surely give us...
不意に
Suddenly,
消えゆく運命でも
even if it's a destiny that fades away,
君が生きている限り
as long as you are living,
命は続く
life goes on,
永遠に
forever.
その力の限り どこまでも
With all its power, everywhere,
私が死ぬとも
Even if I should pass away,
君が生きている限り
as long as you are living,
命は続く
life goes on,
永遠に
forever.
その力の限り どこまでも
With all its power, everywhere,
続く
it continues.
きみの瞳に映る
Reflected in your eyes,
わたしは何色ですか
what color am I?
赤深き望むなら
If you wish for a deep red,
渡そう陽の光を
I will give you the sunlight.
悲しみが溢れ
Sadness overflowed...
瞼閉じました
and I closed my eyes.
こぼれた滴は
The spilled drops...
心に沁みゆく
soak into my heart.
行き渡る波は
The spreading waves...
弱く交えます
mingle weakly.
とどけしゆりかご
The cradle I sent...
眠りをさそう
invites sleep.
夢になつかし
In my dreams, I search...
面影をさがす
for a familiar face.
手を伸ばし 強く
I reach out my hand and...
抱きしめたくなる
I want to hold you tight.
きみの瞳に映る
Reflected in your eyes,
わたしは何色ですか
what color am I?
赤深き望むなら
If you wish for a deep red,
渡そう高き空を
I will give you the high sky.
不安定な神様
Unstable God,
繰り返す出会いと別れ
Repeating meetings and partings.
また会えるその日まで
Until the day we can meet again,
時駆ける旅人
time-traveling traveler.
あなたが泣いている
You are crying.
流るる涙の雨
A rain of flowing tears.
慰めとは言わない
I won't call it comfort.
心悲しくて
With a sad heart,
生きていけぬもの
those who cannot live on,
何かを背負いながら
while carrying something,
見えない鎖に
to invisible chains,
繋がれている
they are connected.
どれほど救われただろう
How much have I been saved?
あどけない笑顔を
That innocent smile,
なくしたくはない
I don't want to lose it.
不安定な神様
Unstable God,
繰り返すことなき運命
a fate that never repeats.
生まれて そして 死んでゆく定め
A destiny of being born and then dying.
かけちがえた世界で
In a world where we missed each other,
繰り返す出会いと別れ
repeating meetings and partings.
また会えるその日まで
Until the day we can meet again,
時駆ける旅人
time-traveling traveler.
戦闘開始！！
Combat Start!!
鳥？
A bird?
デカっ！？
It's huge!?
禍々しき心
An ominous heart,
黒く染めゆきながら
as it stains itself in black,
抑えられなくて
it cannot be suppressed,
解き放たれる
and it's being set free.
何回も
Many times,
名を呼んでいた
I was calling your name.
あどけない笑顔は
That innocent smile,
もうどこにもない
is nowhere to be found anymore.
不安定な神様
Unstable God.
今 引き継いだ
I've now inherited
夢と愛を
these dreams and love.
さあ 盾となり 守り抜くさだめ
Now, it's my destiny to be a shield and protect them all.
かけ違えた世界で
In this world of misunderstandings,
探す旅 引き裂かれても
even if my search is torn apart,
また会えると信じて
I'll believe that we can meet again,
時駆ける旅人
a traveler crossing time.
不安定な神様
Unstable God,
繰り返す過去と未来
repeating the past and the future.
生まれそして死にゆくさだめ
A destiny of being born and then dying.
かけ違えた世界で
In this world of misunderstandings,
繰り返す出会いと別れ
repeating encounters and partings.
また会えるその日まで
Until that day when we can meet again,
時駆ける旅人
a traveler crossing time.
また会えるその日まで
Until that day when we can meet again,
時駆ける旅人
a traveler crossing time.
はい！ということで、Suaraさんにお越しいただき、一緒に歌わせていただきました！
Yes! And so, Suara-san joined me here, and we performed together!
Suaraさん、自己紹介をいただいてもよろしいでしょうか？
Suara-san, would you mind introducing yourself?
はい、Suaraです。
Yes, I'm Suara.
『うたわれるもの』シリーズの主題歌をたくさん歌っている者です！
I'm the one who sings many of the theme songs for the 'Utawarerumono' series!
はい！
Yes!
ようこそー！ Suaraさーん！
Welcome! Suara-san!
こよりさーん！
Koyori-san!
そうなんです、実はですね、
That's right. Actually...
『うたわれるもの』というゲーム、昨年約3ヶ月間かけてシリーズの三部作を実況プレイさせていただいたんですけれど、
last year, over about three months, I did a let's play of the three games in the 'Utawarerumono' series.
その『うたわれるもの』、本当に曲がめちゃくちゃ良いのですが、
The music in 'Utawarerumono' is truly incredible,
その歌をほぼ全てSuaraさんが歌っていらっしゃるというのです！
and Suara-san sings almost every single one of those songs!
はい。
Yes.
もう、耳が今日本当に幸せで！
My ears are just so happy today!
いや、こちらこそですよ、本当に！
No, the pleasure is all mine, really!
もう本当恐縮、恐れ多い状態なんですけれども、
I'm just so honored and humbled by this,
ありがとうございます！
thank you so much!
Thank you!
Suaraさんには実は4周年の時に逆凸でメッセージも頂戴しておりまして、
Actually, I even received a message from Suara-san during my 4th anniversary call-in stream.
その時に「いつか一緒に歌いたい」というのも、こよりも結構熱烈なラブコールをさせていただいていたんですけれど、
At that time, I sent quite a passionate 'love call' saying I wanted to sing together someday.
その思いを本日叶えることができました！
And today, I was able to make that wish come true!
わあー！
Wow!
えっと、あの、ちょっと質問が何個かあるんですけど、
Um, well, I have a few questions for you.
はい。
Yes.
実はあの『うたわれるもの』の実況してた時に、
Actually, while I was doing the 'Utawarerumono' let's play,
最終回でSuaraさんがコメントしてくださいまして！
Suara-san left a comment during the final episode!
はい。
Yes.
こよりの実況をちょっとご覧くださったと思うんですけれど、
I believe you watched a bit of my stream,
はい、そうなんですよ。
Yes, that's right.
見られますか？ 実況とかって普段。
Do you usually watch things like let's plays?
いや、ちょっと実はですね、初めて拝見させていただいて。
Well, to tell you the truth, yours was the first one I'd ever watched.
そうなんですか？！
Really?!
そうなんです。あの、アクアプラスのスタッフの方とかからも、「こよりさんっていう『うたわれ』配信してるよ」って言って、
Yes. Some of the staff from Aquaplus told me, "There's someone named Koyori-san streaming 'Utawarerumono'."
情報は聞いていたんですよね。
So I'd heard about you.
ええー！
Whoa!
で、私のライブに来てくれるファンの方たちからも聞いていたんですよ。
And I'd also heard it from the fans who come to my live shows.
「ぜひ見てみてください」って言って、
They said, "You should definitely check it out."
それで拝見させていただいたっていうのが、最終回だったんですけども。
And so, the one I ended up seeing was that final episode.
そうだったんですね！ 恐縮です！
I see! I'm so honored!
いえいえ、もうすごい、本当に、こよりさんの『うたわれるもの』への愛が溢れてて、
No, no. It was amazing, really. Koyori-san, your love for 'Utawarerumono' was just overflowing,
見てて、もう最後までずっと拝見させていただいて。
and I watched it all the way through to the very end.
わあー！
Wow!
で、「コメント送りたいな」って、でも「早くしないと終わっちゃう！」と思いながら、
And I thought, "I want to send a comment," but also, "If I don't hurry, it'll be over!"
で、同じ部屋に私の息子がいたんですけど、
My son was actually in the same room as me,
あ、はい。息子さんまで！
Ah, yes. Even your son!
息子に「コメント送ってみていいと思う？」って聞いて、
and I asked him, "Do you think it's okay if I send a comment?"
聞いたら、「いいんちゃう？」って言って。
He said, "Sure, why not?"
いい息子さんだー！
What a great son!
それで、もう本当に震える手でコメント打って、もう「早くエンターキーを！」って、
So, with hands that were literally shaking, I typed the comment and thought, "Quick, the Enter key!"
そんな緊張してくださってたんですか？！
You were that nervous?!
「押そうか、押そうか、どうしよう、でも早く押さな！」みたいに。
I was like, "Should I press it? Should I? What do I do? But I have to press it now!"
はい、それでドキドキしながら
Yes, so I was really nervous...
送らせていただいたら
when I sent that message,
コメントに気づいてくださって
but then you noticed my comment.
もうとっても嬉しかったです！
I was so incredibly happy!
こよりもですし、見ていた助手くんたちも
Not just me, but all the assistants watching...
ものすごく嬉しくて
were so happy too.
やっぱり、見ていただけるというのが
The fact that you were watching...
スアラさんとか、アクアプラスさんもそうですし
Suara-san, and even Aquaplus...
公式の皆様にご覧いただけるって
Being seen by the official staff...
本当に嬉しく光栄なことなので
is truly a joy and an honor.
幸せでございました、ありがとうございます！
I was so happy, thank you!
もう、すごい楽しくて見入っちゃいました、本当に
I was having so much fun, I couldn't look away.
嬉しいです！
I'm so glad!
すごい長時間されてるのが、すごいなと思って
It's amazing how you can perform for so long.
あの日の夜も歌枠も聞かせていただいたり
I even listened to your singing stream that night.
あ、そうなんですか！？
Oh, really!?
すごい体力だなぁと思いながら
I was thinking, 'She has incredible stamina!'
楽しんでるのは、うたわれるものが
I was enjoying it because Utawarerumono...
本当に素晴らしい作品だったから、ですので！
is such a wonderful series!
そのうたわれるものと、ずっと付き合っていらっしゃる
Since you've been involved with Utawarerumono...
スアラさんですけれども...
for such a long time, Suara-san...
推しキャラとかっていらっしゃるんですか？
do you have a favorite character?
推しキャラですか？
A favorite character?
推しキャラはやっぱり、ちょっとエルルゥということで...
My favorite would have to be Eruruu...
エルルゥということにしておかないとね...
I have to say Eruruu, otherwise...
ちょっとフォークで刺されるかもしれないんで！
she might stab me with a fork!
あ、あれ！？もしや、あの...
Oh! Wait! Does that mean...
仲が良いっていうのは...
you're close because...
中の方の、柚木涼香さんとね
the person 'inside,' Yuzuki Ryoka-san?
とっても仲良くさせていただいてて
Yes, we're very good friends.
本当に、アニメの放送の時からですね
Actually, ever since the anime aired...
2006年からずっと仲良くさせていただいてるっていう
back in 2006, we've been close.
わー！20年！
Wow! 20 years!
そうですね、20年。
That's right, 20 years.
すごい！それはエルルゥ推しですね！
Amazing! Then you definitely have to support Eruruu!
ということで、エルルゥ推しでお願いします
So, please root for Eruruu with me.
こよりはアルルゥが大好きなので
I love Aruruu,
エルルゥ・アルルゥで、姉妹で！
so Eruruu and Aruruu, the sisters!
嬉しいです！
I'm so happy!
もっともっとお話ししたいんですけれども
I'd love to talk much more,
お時間が来てしまいまして...
but we've run out of time.
本当に今日は、一緒に歌っていただきありがとうございました！
Thank you so much for singing with me today!
こよりさんの本当に柔らかい、優しい、暖かい声に
Koyori-san's truly soft, kind, and warm voice...
包まれながら、私も一緒に歌えて
wrapped around me as we sang together.
本当に幸せでした！
I was truly happy!
恐縮でございました！ありがとうございます！
I'm honored! Thank you!
またぜひ、色々ご一緒させていただける機会があれば
I hope there will be more chances to work together.
ぜひぜひ！よろしくお願いします
Definitely! Looking forward to it.
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
スアラさんでした！ありがとうございました！
That was Suara-san! Thank you!
こよりのリズムラボ
Koyori's Rhythm Lab
9th リミックス
9th Remix
やがて女はきれいになるだろう
Eventually, a woman will become beautiful
だいスキ！
I love you!
行っくよ〜！
Here we go!
とっても媚びてんの人生
Living such a sycophantic life
本当の自分出な〜い
My true self never comes out
甘いドレスがセクシー
The sweet dress is sexy
いい女並んで
Fine women lining up
ちょっとお返しに
In exchange, just a little
ワンモア素敵だよ
One more, it's wonderful
カンカン焼きたい 愛されたい
I want to be radiant, I want to be loved
歴史変えて置かない
I won't leave history unchanged
はかない人生 生きたい
I want to live this fleeting life
あ〜悲しい歌流れる
Ah, a sad song is playing
街のど真ん中歩く
Walking through the center of town
涙溢れちゃう
Tears are overflowing
涙溢れちゃうのあ〜
Tears are overflowing, ah...
どうしてなんだろう
I wonder why
扉破って
Break through the door
誰も信じられなきゃ 泣きたいだけでいい
If you can't believe anyone, just cry
裸になって
Baring it all
もっと恋して
Falling more in love
毒に溺れ過ぎて 周りが見えなくなっていいじゃん
Drowning in poison, losing sight of everything is fine
だいスキ！
I love you!
マジだいスキ！
I really love you!
だいスキ！
I love you!
マジだいスキ！
I really love you!
だいスキ！
I love you!
愛♡スクリーム！
Ai♡Scream!
教えて もっと あなたのこと
Tell me more about you
Tell me mo-mo-mo-mo Tell me mo-mo-mo-mo
聞かせて もっと あなたの声
Let me hear more of your voice
Let me hear mo-mo-mo-mo Let me hear mo-mo-mo-mo
こんなにドキドキ もう抑えきれない
My heart is pounding so much, I can't hold it back
Oh! I need you
友達は卒業 運命の私
Graduating from being friends, my destiny...
見つけてほしいの
...I want you to find me
One 勇気を出して
One, have some courage
Two 見つめる作戦
Two, the staring strategy
Three 目と目が合えば
Three, if our eyes meet...
Four Wow
止められない
Unstoppable
Yeah Yeah Yeah この恋 この愛で
Yeah Yeah Yeah, with this love and affection
Melt Melty 溶けちゃうよ
Melt Melty, I'm melting away
ねぇ？ねぇ？ねぇ？ 気づいて "My darling"
Hey? Hey? Hey? Notice me, "My darling"
届け！ 大好き！
Reach out! I love you!
アイ 愛スクリーム！ Scream 叫びましょ
Love, love, love! Scream, let's scream!
スクリーム！ アイスクリーム！
Scream! Ice cream!
OK! アイ 愛スクリーム！ Scream 叫びましょ
OK! Love, love, love! Scream, let's scream!
スクリーム！ アイスクリーム！
Scream! Ice cream!
こよりちゃん！ はーい！ 何が好き？
Koyori-chan! Yes! What do you like?
マヨネーズ！ よりもあなた！
Mayonnaise! More than that, you!
AZKiちゃん！ はーい！ 何が好き？
AZKi-chan! Yes! What do you like?
こしあん つぶあん よりもあなた！
Smooth or chunky bean paste, I prefer you!
ラミィちゃん！ はーい！ 何が好き？
Lamy-chan! Yes! What do you like?
お酒よりもあなた！
More than alcohol, I like you!
みんな！ はーい！ 何が好き？
Everyone! Yes! What do you like?
もちろん大好き こより！
Of course, we love you, Koyori!
止められない
Unstoppable
Yeah Yeah Yeah この恋 この愛で
Yeah Yeah Yeah, with this love and affection
Melt Melty 溶けちゃうよ
Melt Melty, I'm melting away
ねぇ？ねぇ？ねぇ？ 気づいて "My darling"
Hey? Hey? Hey? Notice me, "My darling"
届け！ 大好き！
Reach out! I love you!
アイ 愛スクリーム！ Scream 叫びましょ
Love, love, love! Scream, let's scream!
スクリーム！ アイスクリーム！
Scream! Ice cream!
OK! アイ 愛スクリーム！ Scream 叫びましょ
OK! Love, love, love! Scream, let's scream!
スクリーム！ アイスクリーム！
Scream! Ice cream!
お願い見つけて "My darling"
Please find me, "My darling"
My darling My darling
お願い気づいて "My darling"
Please notice me, "My darling"
My darling My darling
One 勇気を出して
One, have some courage
Two 近づく作戦
Two, the strategy to get closer
Three 手と手が触れて
Three, if our hands touch...
Four Wow
止められない
Unstoppable
Yeah Yeah Yeah この恋 この愛で
Yeah Yeah Yeah, with this love and affection
Melt Melty 溶けちゃうよ
Melt Melty, I'm melting away
ねぇ？ねぇ？ねぇ？ 気づいて "My darling"
Hey? Hey? Hey? Notice me, "My darling"
それは あなた
That is you
アイ 愛スクリーム！ Scream 叫びましょ
Love, love, love! Scream, let's scream!
スクリーム！ アイスクリーム！
Scream! Ice cream!
OK! アイ 愛スクリーム！ Scream 叫びましょ
OK! Love, love, love! Scream, let's scream!
スクリーム！ アイスクリーム！
Scream! Ice cream!
アイ 愛スクリーム！ Scream 叫びましょ
Love, love, love! Scream, let's scream!
スクリーム！ アイスクリーム！
Scream! Ice cream!
OK! アイ 愛スクリーム！ Scream 叫びましょ
OK! Love, love, love! Scream, let's scream!
スクリーム！ アイスクリーム！
Scream! Ice cream!
RELAY!
もう何十回も 何百回も
Tens of times, hundreds of times already,
澄む空見上げて
I've looked up at the clear sky.
辿り着いた場所が
The place I finally reached
運命のダイヤモンド
is the diamond of destiny.
何千回も 何万回も
Thousands of times, tens of thousands of times,
涙流した君へ
to you who shed tears.
ねぇ 諦められたことはあったっけ？
Hey, was there ever a time you could give up?
憧れは限界だったかな
Was your longing at its limit?
もういらないよ 嘘にただもがくなんて
I don't need it anymore, just struggling with lies.
もったいないでしょ
It's a waste, isn't it?
それぞれの物語 交差する瞬間を
The moment our stories intersect,
見つめる日々は...
the days of staring are...
放った夢だけ 大きな声描いて
Draw only the dreams you've let loose with a loud voice,
弾けそうな煌めきを
with a brilliance that seems ready to burst.
消えることなく どこまででも
Without fading, no matter how far,
世界の向こうに届けてよ
reach out beyond the world.
終わることのない この胸の衝動は
This impulse in my chest that never ends,
どうしてもどうしても 僕を呼んでいたから
because it was calling out to me no matter what.
その先へと 走り続ける
I'll keep running towards what lies ahead,
次へ 次へ
to the next, and the next.
嘘だった中途半端な深い坂超えて
Overcoming the deep slope of halfway lies,
立ち尽くしていた独り 雨はプレリュード
standing still alone, the rain is a prelude.
何千回も 何万回も
Thousands of times, tens of thousands of times,
祈り続けた君へ
to you who kept praying.
ねぇ 聞かせてよ 夢は叶うんだって
Hey, let me hear that dreams do come true.
諦めが完敗ならば 絶望はないよ
If giving up is total defeat, there is no despair.
誰に邪魔されようとも ためらわないで
No matter who tries to stop you, don't hesitate,
託された情熱を 落とさずに繋いでいく
connect the passion entrusted to you without dropping it.
そう 最後まで...
Yes, until the very end...
降りしきる期待 誇り跳ねて
Expectations raining down, pride bouncing,
鳴り止まないファンファーレ
the fanfare that never stops ringing.
いつの心に 流れていた
It was flowing in my heart at some point,
遠い未来へ 祈るよ
I pray for the distant future.
忘れられない あの日々の後悔も
Even the regrets of those unforgettable days,
追いかけて 追いかけて 滑り込んだこの想い
chasing, chasing, this feeling that slid in.
青い空に ふと溢れてた
Suddenly overflowing into the blue sky,
遠く 遠く
far, far away.
目覚めては繰り返す 眠い朝は
Waking up and repeating, on sleepy mornings,
襟のタイをきつく締め
I tighten the tie on my collar.
教室のドアくぐると ほんの少し
Passing through the classroom door, just a little,
胸を張って歩き出せる
I can walk out with my head held high.
そんな日常に 吹き抜ける風
In such a daily life, a wind blows through.
聞こえた気がした 感じた気がしたんだ
I felt like I heard it, I felt like I felt it.
震え出す 今この胸で
Starting to tremble, now in this chest,
来る気がした 幾億の星が
I felt it coming, billions of stars...
消え去って行くのを 見送った
I watched them fade away.
手を振った
I waved my hand
良かったねと
Saying "That's good"
廊下の隅見下ろす
Looking down at the corner of the hallway
掃除の途中
In the middle of cleaning
おかしなものだと想う
I think it's a strange thing
私の中のときは
Even though time inside me...
止まってるのに
...has come to a stop
違う日々を
As if I'm living...
生きてるように
...through different days
埃は雪の
The dust piles up...
ように降り積む
...just like snow
待ってる気がした
I felt like I was waiting
呼んでる気がしたんだ
I felt like I was being called
震えだす
It begins to tremble
今この時が
this very moment
見つけた気がした
I felt like I found it
失われた記憶が
The lost memories...
呼び覚ました
...have been awakened
物語
The story...
永遠の
...of eternity...
その終わり
...has its end
いつの間にか
Before I knew it,
駆け出してた
I started running
あなたに手を
My hand was being...
引かれてた
...pulled by you
昨日は遠く
Yesterday is far away,
明日はすぐ
tomorrow is right there
そんな当たり前に
At such a natural thing,
心が躍った
my heart danced
聞こえた気がした
I felt like I heard it
感じた気がしたんだ
I felt like I felt it
震えだす
It begins to tremble
今この胸で
now in my chest
もう来る気がした
I felt like it was already coming
幾千の朝を越え
Crossing over thousands of mornings...
新しい日が
...a new day
待ってる気がした
I felt like it was waiting
呼んでる気がしたんだ
I felt like I was being called
震えてる
It is trembling,
この魂が
this soul of mine
見つけた気がした
I felt like I found it
幾億の夢のように
Like hundreds of millions of dreams...
消え去る日を
...watching the day...
見送った
...fade away
手を振った
I waved my hand,
ありがとうと
saying "Thank you"
ぽつり灯り 管制塔
A single light, the control tower
砂嵐の向こうへ
Beyond the sandstorm
祈るように綴った
Like a prayer, I wrote down...
これからのこと
...what is to come
管制塔より / 作詞・作曲・編曲 堀江晶太
From the Control Tower / Lyrics, Composition, Arrangement: Shota Horie
ラジオネーム 匿名希望
Radio name: Anonymous
お便り 届いていますか
Is my letter reaching you?
この世界がいつからか
Since when did this world...
まるで他人事のように
...feel like someone else's affair?
やけに静かなので
It's so quiet...
不安になったのです
...that I became anxious
思い出したのです
I remembered
人知れず口を噤んだまま
While secretly keeping my mouth shut
終われないのです
I can't let it end
それは嫌なのです
I don't want that
夢ってもっと
Dreams were supposed to be...
わがままだったでしょう
...more selfish, weren't they?
答えてよ 笑ってよ 気づいてよ
Answer me, laugh, notice me
此処に居るのにな
Even though I'm right here...
意地悪だなぁ
...You're so mean
誰にも届かない光を
A light that reaches no one...
どうしたら伝えられるのでしょう
...How can I ever convey it?
どうしても 伝えたいよ
I want to convey it, no matter what
ラジオリズム 匿名希望
Radio rhythm, anonymous hope
意気地なしなのでしょうか
Am I just a coward?
それともこの世界には 僕はお邪魔なのでしょうか
Or is it that I'm just an obstacle in this world?
だとしても綴るよ
Even so, I'll write it down
みっともなく叫ぶよ
I'll scream it out unsightly
振られたって好きだよ
I still love you even if I'm rejected
いいでしょ
Is that okay?
楽しかったよね
It was fun, wasn't it?
悔しかったよね
It was frustrating, wasn't it?
もう独り言は嫌だ
I don't want to talk to myself anymore
嫌だ
I hate it
「待たせちゃったかな」
"Did I keep you waiting?"
『別に待ってないよ』
"I wasn't really waiting."
夢と呼んだ それも僕だっただけ
What I called a dream, that was just me too
もういいかい
Are you ready?
そういいかい
Is that so?
応えてよ
Answer me
笑ってよ
Laugh with me
気付いてよ
Notice me
此処に居るのにな
Even though I'm right here...
意地悪だな
You're so mean
誰にも届かない光を
A light that reaches nobody
僕だけは光と呼び続ける
Only I will keep calling it a light
真夜中管制塔から
From the midnight control tower...
世界を明かしてやる
I'll illuminate the world
特報
Special News
管制塔より
Kanseitou yori
歌 博衣こよ
Vocals: Hakui Koyori
作詞・作曲 堀江晶太
Lyrics/Composition: Horie Shouta
新アニメーションMV
New Animation MV
博衣こよ 管制塔より
Hakui Koyori - Kanseitou yori
ライブ終了直後 プレミア公開
Premiering immediately after the live
ということで！
And so!
新曲のお披露目 フルアニメーションMV公開の告知 新3Dのお披露目！
New song reveal, animation MV announcement, and new 3D reveal!
3つドドンとまとめさせていただきましたー！イエーイ！
I've packed all three of these together! Yay!
情報量多かったけど ついていけてるかなー？
That was a lot of info, but are you keeping up?
はい ちょっとね 新3Dが可愛すぎて気になっちゃうと思うんですけど
I know the new 3D is so cute it's distracting,
まずはオリ曲の話からさせてください！
but first, let me talk about the original song!
お披露目させていただいたのは 新曲『管制塔より』！
The song I performed was the new song "Kanseitou yori"!
はい！ついにあの堀江晶太さんに書き下ろしていただきました！
Yes! It was finally written for me by Horie Shouta-san!
みんな どうだったー？エモい？良かったー？
Everyone, how was it? Emotional? Good?
はい そしてですね 今ちょっと映像も流して「すごい」って言ってくれてて
Yes, and I'm so happy you're calling the video "amazing,"
このライブ終了直後にフルアニメーションMVがプレミア公開されます！
The full animation MV will premiere right after this live!
多分もうマネちゃんがポチッとしてくれてると思います！
I think my manager is clicking the button as we speak!
世界観がめちゃくちゃこだわられている映像作品になっているので
It's a visual work with a lot of attention to the world-building,
何回も見たり聴いたり そしてちょっと世界観の考察とかしてみてね！
so please watch it many times and try to speculate about the setting!
そして！お待たせしました！新3Dー！
And! Sorry to keep you waiting! The new 3D!
あ ちょっと待って！1個言い忘れました！
Oh, wait! I forgot one thing!
さっきの曲『管制塔より』 24時にリリースもあります！
The song "Kanseitou yori" will also be released at midnight!
よろしくお願いします！
Please check it out!
そしてですね お待たせしました 新3Dー！
And now, sorry to keep you waiting, the new 3D!
どう？可愛い？可愛い？可愛いー？
How is it? Is it cute? Is it cute? Is it cute?
はい！もっとね 余すことなく見せたいんだけど イエーイ！
Yes! I want to show you every bit of it, yay!
ももこママの あの あれ いつもにすごい近くなったんじゃないかなー！
I think it's become very close to Momoko-mama's original design!
この後のメン限ライブでね 撮影会もしちゃいます！
I'll have a photoshoot during the members-only live later!
さらに細かく見せちゃうので ぜひメン限ライブも来てください！
I'll show it in more detail, so please come to that too!
メン限ライブでは本編で歌えなかったあのゲームの曲
In the members-only live, I'll sing that game's song
みんなが大好きな曲 キンキンキンも歌うよ！お楽しみに！
that everyone loves, Kin-Kin-Kin! Look forward to it!
じゃあ1つだけ新3Dのめっちゃ変わったポイント教えちゃうと
So, I'll tell you just one point about the new 3D that's changed...
ケモ耳が揺れます！
The animal ears move!
うおおおおー！可愛いー！
Whoa! So cute!
にー！
Ni!
はい！
Yes!
ということでね
And with that...
えー、あ！
uh, oh!
トレンド1位も本当にありがとうございます！
Thank you so much for trending #1!
今日無理かなーって思ってたんで
I thought it might be impossible today,
めっちゃ嬉しかったし
so I'm really happy.
トレンド爆散
Trends are exploding—
なんかすごいっぱい入ってたみたいで
it seems like so many tags got in!
本当にありがとう！
Thank you so much!
それでは！もう一つ大事なお知らせです！
Now then! There's one more important announcement!
ドン！
Bam!
博衣こより
Hakui Koyori...
誕生日記念グッズ2026が発売されます！
Birthday Merchandise 2026 will be released!
よー！
Yay!
さっそく詳細を見ていきましょう！
Let's check out the details right away!
まず一つ目はこちら！
First, here's this!
もふこよりにもなれる2WAYブランケット！
A 2-way blanket that turns into Mofukoyo!
お部屋でゲームを楽しんでいるこよりの描き下ろしイラストです！
A new illustration of Koyori gaming in her room!
イラストはもちろん
The illustration is, of course,
ももこママ！
by Momoko-mama!
これ丸めるともふこよりに早変わりして
Roll it up and it transforms into Mofukoyo!
持ち運びも楽ちんだし
It's easy to carry around,
そのまま飾っても可愛いですね！
and it's cute to just display it!
続いてはこちら！
Next up is this!
ボイスキーホルダー～ゲーム実況編～！
Voice Keychain - Gameplay Commentary Ver.!
待望のボイスキーホルダーが出ました！
The long-awaited voice keychain is here!
こよりの録り下ろしボイスが入っているもので
It contains newly recorded voices of mine!
今回はライブに合わせて
This time, to match the live performance,
ゲーム実況中っぽいセリフ、絶叫が
lines and screams like a game stream,
6種類入っております！
six types are included!
セリフはこよが考えました！
I thought of the lines myself!
イラストはなもり先生です！
The illustration is by Namori-sensei!
続いてはこちら！
Next up is this!
こより監督ぬいぐるみスマホスタンド！
Koyori Director Plushie Smartphone Stand!
あのこより監督がついにぬいぐるみになったよ！
Koyori Director is finally a plushie!
可愛い！
So cute!
そのまま飾るもよし
You can just display it,
スマホスタンドにもなるので超便利です！
or use it as a phone stand, it's super handy!
絶対ゲットしてねー！
Make sure to get one!
最後はこちら！
Finally, this!
ゲーム機風カードホルダー！
Game Console-Style Card Holder!
特典のチェキ風ブロマイドとか
You can put the bonus bromides
ホロカも入れられて持ち運べちゃうカードホルダーです！
or Holocards in it and carry them around!
中に入っている台紙のイラストはこよちゃんが描きました！
I drew the illustration on the inner paper!
ゲーム機風のデザインもレトロゲームっぽくて可愛くない？
Isn't the retro console design cute?
はい、そしてフルセット特典はこちらです！
Yes, and here's the full set bonus!
ももこママ描き下ろしのチェキ風ブロマイドが付きます！
It comes with a bromide by Momoko-mama!
数量限定版は直筆サインと箔押し
The limited edition has a hand-written signature,
複製メッセージ入り！
and a printed message with foil stamping!
通常版は箔押しの複製サインとメッセージ入りになってます！
The regular version has the printed message/signature!
販売開始が、この後21時10分にしてあるので
Sales start soon at 9:10 PM,
皆さんあの慌てないで大丈夫です！
so everyone, please don't rush! It's okay!
10分からなので！はい、あの見てってください！
It's from 10 past! Please check it out!
よろしくお願いします！さらに特典ASMRボイスも付きます！
Thank you! Plus, there's a bonus ASMR voice!
毎年恒例の君の誕生日を逆に祝っちゃう
The annual ASMR voice where I celebrate
ASMRボイス2026年版！
your birthday instead, 2026 edition!
こちらですね、毎年みんな誕生日まで我慢して
Every year, everyone waits until their birthday
聴いて「わーい」ってなっていうの
to listen to it and get all excited,
すごく嬉しく思ってます！
which makes me very happy!
ぜひゲットしてください！
Please be sure to get it!
はい、ということでね
Alright, so with all that,
怒涛のお知らせでしたが
that was a ton of news!
可愛いでしょ？
Cute, right?
みんなが可愛いって言ってくれてて
Everyone is saying I'm cute,
こよ嬉しいよー！
it makes me so happy!
表情とかもちょっと変わったんですよ
My expressions have changed a bit too.
にひゃー！
Niya~!
これが「できにゃ」になりました！
This became "Deki-nya"!
あとは「きりっ」！
Also, "Kiri~"!
いぇーい！こんな表情もできるようになりました！
Yay! I can make these expressions now!
面源をお楽しみに！
Look forward to the member stream!
ということで今日は博衣こより生誕ライブ2026
Anyway, for the Hakui Koyori Birthday Live 2026,
ゲームソングライブに見に来てくれてありがとう！
thanks for coming to the Game Song Live!
この後ですね、新曲のアニメMV公開と
After this, we have the new song MV release
面源ライブ、あ、ですね
and the member stream, uh...
アニメMV公開見て、で10分からグッズ買って
Watch the MV, then buy the goods from 10 past,
15分から面源ライブって感じで
and the member stream from 15 past.
ゆっくり順番にいけるようになっているので
You can go through them slowly in order,
慌てず、駆けず、何だっけ？
so don't rush, don't run, what was it?
押さずでよろしくお願いします！
And don't push! Please!
ということで今日はちょっと遅れちゃったんだけど
So, though it started a bit late today,
この新3Dお披露目して
I'm happy I could show this new 3D,
生誕ライブもできて
do my birthday live,
大好きなゲームソングいっぱいお披露目できて
and perform many of my favorite game songs!
嬉しかったよ！みんな本当に見に来てくれてありがとう！
I'm so glad! Thank you all for coming to see me!
また会おうね！
Let's meet again!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
MV見てねー！
Watch the MV!
ばいばーい！
Bye-bye!